const qbank = [
  {
      QuestionID: "2",
      Question: "An algebraic expression containing three terms is called a",
      Option1: "monomial",
      Option2: "binomial",
      Option3: "trinomial",
      Option4: "all of these",
      CorrectOption: "3",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Easy"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "3",
      Question: "Number of terms in the expression 3.x^2.y - 2.y^2.z - z^2.x + 5 is",
      Option1: "2",
      Option2: "3",
      Option3: "4",
      Option4: "5",
      CorrectOption: "3",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Easy"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "4",
      Question: "The terms of expression 4.x^2 - 3.x.y are:",
      Option1: "4.x^2 and -3.x.y",
      Option2: "4.x^2 and 3.x.y",
      Option3: "4.x^2 and -x.y",
      Option4: "x^2 and x.y",
      CorrectOption: "1",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Easy"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "5",
      Question: "Factors of -5.x^2.y^2.z are",
      Option1: "-5.x.y.z",
      Option2: "-5.x^2.y.z",
      Option3: "-5.x.x.y.y.z",
      Option4: "-5.x.y.z^2",
      CorrectOption: "3",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Medium"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "6",
      Question: "Coefficient of x in -9.x.y^2.z is",
      Option1: "9.y.z",
      Option2: "-9.y.z",
      Option3: "9.y^2.z",
      Option4: "-9.y^2.z",
      CorrectOption: "4",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Medium"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "7",
      Question: "The subtraction of 5 times of y from x is",
      Option1: "5x - y",
      Option2: "y - 5x",
      Option3: "x - 5y",
      Option4: "5y - x",
      CorrectOption: "3",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Easy"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "8",
      Question: "The side length of the top of a square table is x. The expression for perimeter is:",
      Option1: "4 + x",
      Option2: "2x",
      Option3: "4x",
      Option4: "8x",
      CorrectOption: "3",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Medium"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "9",
      Question: "The expression for the number of diagonals that we can make from one vertex of a n sided polygon is:",
      Option1: "2n + 1",
      Option2: "n - 2",
      Option3: "5n + 2",
      Option4: "n - 3",
      CorrectOption: "4",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Hard"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "10",
      Question: "123.x^2.y - 138.x^2.y is a like term of",
      Option1: "10.x.y",
      Option2: "-15.x.y",
      Option3: "-15.x.y^2",
      Option4: "10.x^2.y",
      CorrectOption: "4",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Hard"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "11",
      Question: "The value of 3.x^2 - 5.x + 3 when x = 1 is",
      Option1: "1",
      Option2: "0",
      Option3: "-1",
      Option4: "11",
      CorrectOption: "1",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Easy"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "12",
      Question: "(2^20 Ã· 2^15) Ã— 2^3 =",
      Option1: "2^15",
      Option2: "2^8",
      Option3: "2^5",
      Option4: "None of these",
      CorrectOption: "2",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Hard"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "13",
      Question: "(5/6)^0 =",
      Option1: "1",
      Option2: "6/5",
      Option3: "0",
      Option4: "None of these",
      CorrectOption: "1",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Easy"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "14",
      Question: "(2^2)^n = (2^3)^4, then n = ",
      Option1: "4",
      Option2: "3",
      Option3: "12",
      Option4: "6",
      CorrectOption: "4",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Medium"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "15",
      Question: "(-7/5)^-1 =",
      Option1: "5/7",
      Option2: "-5/7",
      Option3: "7/5",
      Option4: "None of these",
      CorrectOption: "2",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Medium"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "16",
      Question: "81^5 Ã· (3^2)^5 =",
      Option1: "3^10",
      Option2: "3^2",
      Option3: "3^5",
      Option4: "None of these",
      CorrectOption: "1",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Medium"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "17",
      Question: "(8^2 Ã— 8^4) - 2^18 =",
      Option1: "2^2",
      Option2: "2^4",
      Option3: "0",
      Option4: "None of these",
      CorrectOption: "3",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Hard"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "18",
      Question: "(3^7) Ã· (81 Ã— 3^3) =",
      Option1: "3",
      Option2: "3^2",
      Option3: "3^0",
      Option4: "None of these",
      CorrectOption: "3",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Hard"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "19",
      Question: "(1/4)^-3 - (1/3)^-3 =",
      Option1: "37",
      Option2: "1/37",
      Option3: "-37",
      Option4: "-1/37",
      CorrectOption: "1",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Medium"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "20",
      Question: "(10 Ã— 5^(n+1)+ 25 Ã— 5^n) Ã· (3 Ã— 5^(n+2)+ 10 Ã— 5^(n+1))",
      Option1: "3/5",
      Option2: "1",
      Option3: "0",
      Option4: "5",
      CorrectOption: "1",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Hard"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "21",
      Question: "(-1)^50 Ã— (-1)^51 Ã— (1)^100 Ã— (-1)^101 =",
      Option1: "-1",
      Option2: "1",
      Option3: "0",
      Option4: "2",
      CorrectOption: "2",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Easy"
  },
  {
      QuestionID: "22",
      Question: "Find the mode for the data set, which shows the heights( in inches ) of 10 students in a class: 60, 65, 63, 62, 65, 70, 62, 68, 60, 65",
      Option1: "62",
      Option2: "65",
      Option3: "70",
      Option4: "60",
      CorrectOption: "2",
      MarksAllocated: "1",
      DifficultyLevel: "Hard"
  }
]


export default (diff, n = 4) =>
        Promise.resolve(qbank.filter(qs=>qs.DifficultyLevel.includes(diff)).sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));

